Great job. If you made it this far, it
means you successfully made it through
the hardest part in my opinion of this
entire course. You made it through the
promises section. Good job. Give
yourself a hand of applause.
Uh pat yourself on the back. You made
it. Um so why did we go through that
gauntlet? Um the reason we went through
that is because anytime you want to get
external data, you're working with
promises. Um, and if you go on to do
some back-end development, if you want
to connect to a database, you're doing
promises. If you're doing front-end
development and you want to connect to a
server, you're handling promises.
Promises are everywhere in your code.
And even you can occasionally offset
some of your code into asynchronous code
so that it can run behind the scenes.
And how do you handle that? Promises.
And so, you really had to understand
promises. Now, we're going to be
gathering data. Now that you understand
promises, we're going to be gathering
data from external sources. And in order
to do that, you had to know promises.
So, if you made it this far, good job.
Give yourself a pat on the back. And
let's get into it.